A sorry letter?
For Billy?
Oh, it's a song.
- Did you forget something?
- Here.
I have millions of followers
across all social media platforms.
I can ask them to repost it.
Why are you doing this?
Because I still…
Let's wait for Mommy.
[ENRICO] Dear, please hear me out.
[BILLY] That's not necessary.
Let this be the last time
we see each other.
We were doing fine,
weren't we, Auntie Pres?
We were doing just fine.
He's ruining everything.
We were doing fine.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[KNOCKING]
Yes, Auntie?
Are you going to file a case?
Yes, Auntie.
If he won't stay away from me
and my brother.
Termination of Parental Authority
on the grounds of neglect and abandonment.
Is that for me?
It's for the sanctuary.
I got it.
And you don't have to come in tomorrow.
I know you have a lot on your mind.
- Don't worry about it.
- No, it's all right, Auntie.
It's okay.
I have a responsibility to the sanctuary.
I can do this.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
I still think about my husband.
[SNIFFLES]
Even though…
Even though he cheated on me…
[SNIFFLES]
…and left me,
I still want to get back together.
For our child's sake.
I'm pregnant.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Mommy, you're pregnant?!
[CHUCKLES]
[GASPS, EXCLAIMS]
We'll be having two kids to take care of.
Please don't leave us anymore.
Just stay here, Dad.
Don't work on the ship anymore.
- Mm-hmm.
- [BOTH CHUCKLE, GIGGLE]
[YOUNG BILLY SQUEALS]
[YOUNG BILLY] Please don't leave us, Dad!
[CRYING] Please.
[YOUNG BILLY] Mommy, please--
Don't waste your tears on worthless men.
[SOBS] I don't want
my child to be fatherless.
My child deserves a complete family.
I understand you, Gelica.
There is nothing wrong with wanting
a complete family for your child.
However, don't rush into
making a decision.
Especially after
everything you've been through.
But it is difficult to raise
a child on your own.
Maybe you can still work it out.
Give your husband another chance.
Gelica?
If you're willing
to give him another chance,
he should earn it.
Not through words or promises,
but through action.
He should show that he'll be responsible
and make things right.
If he ever does it again,
if he ever leaves you again,
it will hurt a lot more.
And it will hurt your child too.
What matters most right now
is you and your baby.
We are all here to support you.
We want the best for you.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
You had a lot of jobs
in Canada, Mr. Dominguez.
How come you never
stayed at one job for long?
Um, to be honest, ma'am,
I was undocumented.
Oh…
But I stayed because I had to
provide for my family back here.
Why did you come back?
My children are all grown up.
They can support themselves now.
And I also want to spend time with them,
and to keep working,
so I'm not a burden to them.
Actually, ma'am,
I have a lot of experience
as a canteen supervisor
at Maplewood University in Canada.
Ah…
Out of all the applicants,
you are the most qualified.
But…
we won't be able to match
your salary in Canada.
Don't expect too much,
Mr. Dominguez. [CHUCKLES]
Money is not an issue for me.
I just want a job.
I can start now, ma'am.
I can keep track of
the inventory and sales.
Could I take a look at the menu?
I can see how we can improve it
while keeping it within the guidelines
and the kids' budget.
Wow, okay.
You can start today, Mr. Dominguez.
Thank you. Thank you, ma'am.
I'll need your police clearance,
all right?
Ah, ma'am…
Can I submit that later?
Oh, okay. No problem.
- Thank you.
- [CHUCKLES] Thank you.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
I am so proud of you, my dear.
I know you're going through
a lot with your dad,
but you didn't give in to
your emotions earlier.
Your advice will be a big help for Gelica.
I just don't want anyone to experience
what Oliver and I went through.
Not all fathers are like ours. Right?
Hopefully, her husband has changed,
so their family can still be together.
I know you're still hurting.
Can you still do this?
I can.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC TURNS TENSE]
What happened?
My mother's not doing well.
Sometimes, she's quiet.
Unresponsive.
Then she will get violent all of a sudden.
That explains my bruise.
Abi, maybe she needs professional help?
You mean a mental facility?
It wouldn't be possible.
I don't have a budget for that.
My internet cafe
isn't making enough money.
We can assess your mom here.
We could do that for you.
Then we can refer her
to mental health facilities
or community-based services.
Ms. Precious, I know my mother.
She'll refuse
any kind of assessment or test.
What I need is another source of income.
My internet cafe isn't making money.
It's going bankrupt.
Ms. Billy, maybe…?
Sorry, Abi, but there's
no vacancy at LoveList.
Uh, what about here at Angels of Grace?
I have a degree in marketing.
Uh…
I know about
computer hardware and software.
I'm the one who fixes the computers
in my shop when needed.
But our volunteers here
only receive an allowance.
It's not even enough to cover
their transportation and food.
Don't worry, Abi.
If there's an opening at LoveList,
you'll be the first to know.
- Really, Ms. Billy?
- Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[TONI] Based on our estimate,
the initial investment allocation
for this new feature
allows us to scale
without affecting our cash flow.
Bills? Are you still with us?
Yes! Yes! Of course I am.
Um, Charm, do you have
the competitor analysis?
For today, I suggest we zero in on this.
Pebblng has received
a lot of positive reception
because of their newly-launched
Heart Reward Scheme.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
So every successful match
gets a free dinner
at their partner restaurants.
Exactly.
So the free dinner incentive works
even though
there's no way to verify
if those are actual successful matches?
[CHARM] Yes, chief.
Those successful matches
could just be friends
who pretended to match for a free dinner.
- So it's easy to fake it.
- Right.
[BILLY] But attention is currency.
The data will show if it worked.
So, what's your plan, Billy?
Why do you seem quite calm?
[BILLY] Okay.
Okay.
Actually, when I heard about
the Heart Reward Scheme,
I knew it would be trouble.
So I did my homework.
I researched, and I went back
to our previous FGDs.
And one thing kept coming up.
People don't just want matches.
They want something real.
But how?
A wedding?
If we are the real deal,
we won't just be with them
until the first date.
We'll be with them until the wedding.
They give them free dinners.
We give them a wedding package.
- [CLAPS]
- Awesome!
I love it!
[VALERIE] Because it's like
we're giving a statement too.
Because, you know,
you can't just fake a wedding.
- Yes.
- Which proves that…
LoveList is the real deal.
So for those who meet through LoveList
and decide to get married,
we'll pay for it.
- So lit, chief. I'm so in!
- How cool!
- That's brilliant!
- [TONI] But!
That's expensive.
Not if we do it right.
We bring in sponsors, caterers,
wedding gown designers,
and everything else!
[VALERIE] I can cover that.
There's actually a lot of deals coming my
way. People are begging for a collab.
So, yeah. I'll make the calls.
Okay! Thank you, Val.
[VALERIE] Yeah. And Toni!
This is going to be good for you and Yani,
because isn't he a struggling painter?
I mean, I don't mean to offend you,
but for sure, you'll have
a tight budget for your reception.
You might only
serve pancit then. [GIGGLES]
But I mean, you don't have to worry
because this is all for free now.
So, it's perfect, right? [VALERIE GIGGLES]
[FORCED LAUGH] Perfect!
- [VALERIE GIGGLING]
- Val…
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Charm, please include this for our meeting
with Ms. Lindsay on Friday.
Okay.
But…
what should we call this?
So, LoveList has LoveLine and LoveSpeak.
Now, it also has…
LoveFeast.
What do you guys think?
- Good! LoveFeast!
- LoveFeast!
- LoveFeast is good, yes?
- [CHEERING]
- [SQUEALING, WHOOPING]
- LoveFeast!
You know what, Suzie?
I'm learning how to box now.
Wow! Just like Manny Pacquiao?
Isn't that painful?
That's what the gloves are for.
Ah, so you're learning that
to be prepared for Biboy?
So I can protect you.
Really?
Aww.
Okay, let me teach you.
First, here's a straight punch.
That's a straight punch.
And then, this is a hook.
[SUZIE] Ah, I know that one. Boom!
[CHUCKLING]
What are you doing? You do boxing now?
Do you really think you can handle me now?
Do you really want to know?
Would you like to be suspended again?
Boy, he's acting tough!
You've got some nerve, huh?!
That's enough!
I saw what you did.
Would you like me to report you?
- Go away.
- Sorry, sir!
- Sorry! Sorry!
- Let's go!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Thank you, sir.
Oh, by the way, I'm--
I'm Eric. I was recently hired
as a canteen supervisor.
- And you, what's your name?
- I'm Oliver.
Oliver? Oh, Oliver!
Oliver.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
And she's my friend, Suzie.
- Hello, sir.
- Hello.
If someone tries
to mess with you here again,
you know where to find me, okay?
I'll be here in the canteen.
Thank you again, Sir Eric.
- Thank you, sir.
- Thank you very much.
- All right.
- Let's go, Suzie.
[GENTLE MUSIC FADING]
[VALERIE] Billy!
Oh, yes, Val?
So, I called Floramour already
for the flower arrangements
because they've been nagging me
for how many months already,
and they're so glad
that I called them back.
But yes, anyways, good news.
They're very excited to be
a part of the LoveFeast project.
Wow! That's really good news.
Val, thank you.
No.
Thank you.
Because after all the dramas
and what I did to you,
you really covered for me.
Everyone else doubted me, but not you.
It's really nice
to have someone believe in me.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
I think we should really be besties!
- Yeah? [GIGGLES]
- [BILLY CHUCKLES FAINTLY]
Have some coffee first.
You look too serious.
Yes. Thank you.
[BILLY] Are you busy?
Not really.
Oh, dude. I spoke to
Attorney Elle about the case.
Mm-hmm.
She managed to get her hands
on the police records of Caloy Toledo.
[JORDAN] He used to be
the leader of a street gang.
Involved in robbery,
harassment, extortion…
Honestly, I'm not surprised.
He was even implicated in a fight
that resulted in a casualty.
But no one pursued the case.
Wow.
When are you meeting Caloy again?
Next week.
The subpoena has already been issued.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Sir Jordan, excuse me.
The server traffic has tripled.
The login rate and match requests
are too high!
Okay, that's fine.
We may need auto-scaling
or temporary load balancing
to avoid crashing the site.
I'll check it in a bit.
Okay, sir.
The system is flooding!
It's a good problem to have.
- Is that so?
- Congrats, dude.
- Are you still handling things well?
- Yes.
You're dealing with your bar,
with Grandpa Jude,
with Caloy's case,
and now, this.
I mean, can we afford to hire
one more person for the tech team?
[VEHICLES HONKING]
[CALOY] Abi!
What?
What's that?
[PAPER RUSTLES]
- Ouch!
- I told you so!
See? You had him locked up.
He won't leave you alone.
I wouldn't be surprised
if they found out
more information about you.
- You are so stubborn!
- [SCOFFS]
They can dig all they want.
Hey!
They won't find anything on us.
What will they find on me?
On you? Nothing!
And that driver won't say anything.
Don't worry about it.
I'll take care of it.
You better make sure of that.
That hurt, you know. Can I get a kiss?
- Come on.
- You want a kiss?
- Nice try!
- Ow!
- That hurt.
- [PHONE RINGS]
Cut it out.
Look.
[RINGING CONTINUES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[ABI CLEARS THROAT]
Hello, Ms. Billy Idol?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
You have a university degree?
Yes, Ms. Billy.
I graduated in 2014. Cum laude.
[CHUCKLES]
It says here
that your first internship
and your first job was at PhilComm Press.
Tell me about your experience.
That was a great experience
for me, Ms. Billy.
PhilComm Press is one of
the top three media companies in Asia.
I was one of the five interns
from our batch.
After my internship,
they eventually hired me.
Abi.
Most of your experience is in marketing.
How did you develop an interest in IT?
[CHUCKLES] Sir Handsome,
my father was into tech.
He had a gadget repair shop.
That's how I got into tech as well.
I don't have formal training.
I'm self-taught.
Okay.
Since you have your own internet cafe,
you must know a lot about data privacy.
So the question is,
how would you protect
our users' personal data,
like private messages, profiles, etc.?
Encryption is key.
Use HTTPS to protect data in transit
and encrypt your database
to protect data at rest.
Strong authentication, restricted access,
so your system doesn't get hacked.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
Piece of cake.
Okay, let's move on to the performance.
- Mm-hmm.
- Let's say…
the matchmaking feature slows down…
Mm-hmm.
…during peak traffic hours.
What would you do?
Check the server first.
Or you can go straight to
enabling auto-scaling
so it can keep up with the traffic spike.
Ah, I would check the server first.
Or we can go straight to
enabling auto-scaling
so it can keep up with the traffic spike.
That's right.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Okay, so I think we can
wrap up this meeting.
We'll review your application.
Thank you so much for your time, Abi.
Thank you, Ms. Billy Idol.
Thank you. [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Sir Handsome, thank you, thank you.
- Thanks, Abi.
- I really hope I get it.
I want to be a part of LoveList.
Please, Ms. Billy. [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Thanks again.
I'll wait for your call, Ms. Billy.
- Mm-hmm.
- Thank you again, idol.
Sir Handsome, thank you.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC SWELLS]
Jordan and I were impressed with her.
Well, there's nothing wrong with
verifying the information
on her resume, right?
Sorry for giving you more work.
Why did you ask me to check this?
Human Resources could've done this.
Because I know you
had a bad feeling about her.
And now is your chance…
To prove I'm onto something.
To be honest, Charm,
I find her odd too.
At first, it was okay.
You know, it was flattering.
But after a while…
It started getting weird?
There you go.
So why let her apply for a job?
You feel sorry for her.
Hmm?
I want to help her.
[SIGHS SOFTLY]
But, you know,
there's really something about her.
Then I guess let's see.
Let's see if she deserves
to be given a chance.
Okay.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- I'll introduce you to Sir Eric.
- [BILLY] Okay.
Oliver just wanted
to give something to Sir Eric.
[JORDAN] I want him
to go to jail.
For what he did to my friend.
- I was just following orders!
- Who gave you those orders?
Sorry I can't be there with you.
Don't worry about me.
I got this.
Good luck.
[ABI] I'm going to be part of
the LoveList family.
I'm reviewing Abi's resume.
She's lying to us!
[ALARM RINGS]
Don't panic! Let's exit
calmly, okay?
[ALARM BLARING]